<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Casa Blanquita - English version</title>
    <link>https://casablanquita-2859c.web.app/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Casa Blanquita - English version</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 29 Mar 2022 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://casablanquita-2859c.web.app/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Casa Blanquita</title>
      <link>https://casablanquita-2859c.web.app/post/intro/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 29 Mar 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://casablanquita-2859c.web.app/post/intro/</guid>
      <description>Casa Blanquita started in 2017 as part of a family adventure. We wanted to venture into a new work project but make it completely our own.&#xA;The house is a traditional Molinaseca dwelling, built in 1912. We know the date because on the second floor balcony of the main facade there are the initials &amp;ldquo;R.B.&amp;rdquo; and the date 1912. These initials correspond to Ramón Balboa, a well-known man in Molinaseca at the beginning of the 20th century.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rooms</title>
      <link>https://casablanquita-2859c.web.app/post/rooms/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Apr 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://casablanquita-2859c.web.app/post/rooms/</guid>
      <description>The first floor is intended for living-dining room and open kitchen, having a small play area and a toilet.&#xA;Each of the upper floors has a full bathroom and two large bedrooms, making a total of 4 bedrooms and two bathrooms, which can sleep up to 10 people (12 on request), having two rooms with a double bed and a futon and the other two rooms with two beds and an extra bed each.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Location &amp; Surroundings</title>
      <link>https://casablanquita-2859c.web.app/post/location/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Apr 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://casablanquita-2859c.web.app/post/location/</guid>
      <description>Molinaseca is one of the most typical villages of the Camino de Santiago, 6 km from the city of Ponferrada, located in the region of El Bierzo.&#xA;The village itself is a jewel of traditional architecture, with church, hermitage and the famous Roman bridge that crosses the river Meruelo and is crossed, in turn, each year by thousands of pilgrims who immediately enter its famous Real Calle Camino de Santiago.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Awards and badges</title>
      <link>https://casablanquita-2859c.web.app/post/awards/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 07 Apr 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://casablanquita-2859c.web.app/post/awards/</guid>
      <description>Thanks to all the customers who have passed by the house and have spent a few minutes giving us their grain of sand, we have received the great recognition of having one of the best grades in rural accommodation, with a total of 9.7 out of 10.&#xA;All our life we have been surrounded by animals and, therefore, we decided that our house would also be suitable for them. Precisely because of this, we belong to Travelmyth, a hotel metasearch engine for the sophisticated traveler.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Availability and prices</title>
      <link>https://casablanquita-2859c.web.app/post/availability/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Feb 2012 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://casablanquita-2859c.web.app/post/availability/</guid>
      <description>Availability Prices for a maximum of 10 people Season Dates Price July 1st to August 31st, December 21st to January 6th and Easter Week 24 €/person per night (minimum three nights) Rest of the year Dates out of high season 22 €/person per night Booking and rental conditions Rental of complete house: 4 bedrooms, 6 beds (2 of them double beds), 2 extra beds and a cradle. The minimum price to be paid will be 94€ during the whole year except for high season when the price will be 98€.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
